{
    "lvl6": [
        {
            "question": "Finish the declaration for the main method: public static ____ main(String [] args)",
            "answer": "void",
            "id": 1   
        },
        {
            "question": "Finish the code to print out the message on a new line: System.out._______('Hello World')",
            "answer": "println",
            "id": 2   
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of loop iterates or repeates while a condition is stays true",
            "answer": "while",
            "id": 3   
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of loop iterates or repeates and performs at least once while a condition stays true?",
            "answer": "do-while",
            "id": 4   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank for taking in a float as an input: scan._________();",
            "answer": "nextFloat",
            "id": 5   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank for the import of the scanner class: import java.util._______; ",
            "answer": "Scanner",
            "id": 6   
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the size(bytes) of the data type 'double' in Java?" ,
            "answer": "8",
            "id" :7
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the size(bytes) of the data type 'char' in Java?" ,
            "answer": "2",
            "id" :8
        },
        {
            "question":"State True or False. Every IF statement must be followed by an ELSE of ELSE-IF statement." ,
            "answer": "false",
            "id" :9
        },
        {
            "question":"State True or False. A Single-Line comment or Multiline-comment is allowed in between if () and Left Brace ( { )." ,
            "answer": "true",
            "id" :10
        }
    ]
}